Wake up, child.
For today, we're making a floor.
We're making a ceiling.
And perhaps also walls.
Idle hands is the devil's work or something.
Today we're going to be active.
I have big plans.
Massive plans.
Father Oliver.
That's right.
I'm your dad.
I will adopt you.
Nice cogs, I know.
Much better now.
There were too many people saying the cogs were laggy.
When they were in fact not laggy.
So now I made them less laggy looking.
You like that?
Time for some Minecraft.
The cogs are spectacular.
I know.
Will this joke ever get old?
I wonder.
Can we go an entire stream without making that joke?
You think that's possible?
You guys need to come up with something that is a little more funny.
I mean, it is kind of funny, but, you know, I need something more funny.
You can think about it.
For next time.
Let that be your homework.
What was the first song?
I don't remember the name of it.
But it is from Starcraft 2.
It is a Terran theme.
Pretty good.
The current song is from the Talos Principle.
Also... I don't know.
Something's wrong with my throat.
I ate some gnocchi just before.
And for some reason, it didn't really sit well.
In my throat.
Something about it.
I may have to mute myself a couple times as we go.
But it was good.
Gnocchi was good.
I have no coke today.
I only have iced tea.
But I have iced cubes.
Cheers on that one, then.
But I'm stealthy with the mute, so you never know.
Okay.
Let's get it going.
Cheers.
I had to unplug my mouse.
It was... running out of battery.
You know?
You can't play with a mouse that's plugged in.
That's... that's way too... 2010.
Oh, man.
My mouse feels so free now, all of a sudden.
Oh!
What a nice feeling.
I can't believe I made an extra one of those.
Today, guys, we're making floors and ceilings.
I know I discovered a bunch of new shit last time.
Hold on.
There we go.
Um... but I'm gonna... I'm gonna delay that a little bit.
I am very excited about, uh... having belts now.
We're gonna make them, of course.
But not yet.
I wanna get this damn house out of the way before I start making something crazy with belts, you know?
We gotta get the basics in order here.
We just gotta do it.
In fact, you know what?
Let's make a roof.
I like the roof concept.
Uh... but first we gotta empty our shit.
Paper...
Need to sort this inventory.
Dried kelp is the new discovery.
It's a big discovery.
Gold is in here.
Chickens... uh... equip those.
Uh... I guess we can have the goggles on.
That's fine.
Put this here.
Yeah, I don't need that right now.
Boat.
Toolbox, I'll carry around.
Definitely.
Now, all of these we can turn into blocks.
Let's actually do that.
That is much smarter.
Red.
Block.
Yeah, much better.
Okay.
Ingots.
Casings!
Oh, we gotta make a lot of those today.
If we can do it.
This is for the inside.
What else is for the inside?
This one.
Oh, I also have steaks.
Uh...
Yeah, I'm gonna save the steaks for later.
I'm gonna keep my chickens for...
when I do constructions at home.
Potion.
Oh, the potion goes in the box inside.
Uh...
We don't need water bucket right now, either.
Sandpaper is kinda huge.
Actually, that comes with me as well.
Let's put that...
here.
Oh, the deployer is...
a good development.
Rails?
Not now.
Yellow bed.
Uh...
We have a bed here.
So we don't need that right now, either.
What is this clipboard?
A swamp kill enderman.
Right.
That's true.
Let's hang that inside.
Wait, how do I...
Ah, there we go.
Apparently, you can't put it behind that.
Don't know why.
Okay.
We don't need a shield, either.
Not right now.
Minecart is also not needed right now.
These three go inside.
And then we bring wood!
A lot of it.
I may go, uh...
crank it.
In a while here.
Cause I need more wood.
In fact, I need so much wood, I'm gonna...
Keep...
No, wait.
Keep one stack.
Turn the rest...
into planks.
That's how many planks I'll need.
So the problem right now is, I did not actually calculate this properly.
Um...
I'm trying...
I'm gonna make the roof with the staircase.
I was thinking of making the flat roof, you know?
With the greenery on top, but...
Nah, we gotta go for the...
For the...
For the nice roof.
We gotta put in the effort here.
Staircase.
Oh, we need a lot.
Maybe not that much.
Let's take like half of this out.
Actually, we're gonna need way more.
There we go.
That may not even be enough.
We'll see.
Now I need to decide, how do I actually angle this roof?
Um...
So we have three sections, right?
We have this one...
That one and this one.
Maybe we'll make one of them flat.
No, no, no.
Stick to the normal roof.
This one...
If we can do it like this...
And then we can even angle one of them differently.
So that would be...
This...
And then here I'll have to decide.
Also, I need to calculate real quick.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten...
Ooh!
That's actually already good, I think.
I think we're chilling on that one.
Let me see.
Yeah.
I'm gonna have to...
Let me think.
How do I do this properly?
What is the best way to do this?
Let me start from one side.
So obviously here, right?
So there.
There.
Oops.
No.
Let's do...
Here.
And...
Wait.
Oh, I hate...
Calculating this.
I'm so bad at this.
I really am.
But if I go like that...
Actually, that's good.
Yeah.
And then we're gonna go...
Uh...
Here?
Is that gonna...
Let me see.
So...
Here.
Mm-mm.
But actually, that's good.
That's actually okay.
I think.
Yeah, this will be fine.
We're totally chilling.
Let me see.
Let me extend it a little bit, of course.
Maybe I don't like this pillar here.
Nah, keep it as it is and just apply the roof.
It can't be that hard.
Oh, I can just use this.
No, I can't.
I need to have nothing in my hand.
But I can do this!
Yepsy-daisy.
Hey!
That's actually a good way to just...
Unequip the main hand.
Just press F.
Much easier.
Let's make the bottom part first.
Like, I am aware it's gonna be a little brown, you know?
We're gonna have to embellish this with some colors.
But we gotta get the basics down first, you know?
Honestly, I feel good about this.
Oops.
Before I do this side, I really should do the other side first.
Just to see if they align properly.
Is that correct?
It is not correct.
Here.
Let me just do one.
So we do like this.
This is temporary.
Yes.
Is that getting a little too crazy?
Maybe it's too tall.
Hmm.
Not sure if I like this.
Wait, what?
Oh!
Hey!
It's gonna fit!
The problem is...
Or the question is, is it aligned?
You know, get this tree out of here.
I can't see shit.
I'm gonna need my hole.
What is this green stuff?
Why is that there?
There.
There was no tree here.
Oh shit.
Ah!
Okay, there we go.
Look at that!
Fucking aligned and everything!
First try?
Not bad.
And now we go one further.
Very good.
I need to ascend here.
This one is wrong.
Stop doing that!
Why are you doing that?
Oh, it's because of this.
We're gonna speed roof!
Yeah.
As soon as we get this done, the rest is gonna fall into place in no time.
Yeah!
Look at that!
Wonderful!
Oh shit.
It's gonna be so fast.
No!
Damn it!
I'm still not an expert on how to properly align these clicks here.
Wait, here.
And there.
I wonder if there's an easier way.
Let me think.
Maybe it's better to just make the top part, like this.
All the way over.
And then you go down afterward, you know?
Efficiency.
Let me think.
How far do I go?
Oh, definitely to there at least.
Beautiful.
Oh, we're gonna be so fast now!
The next one may be a little problematic, because I have to...
Wait.
Check this out.
Oh, yeah, that's the way.
Very good.
Ultra fast.
Oh, I should just use middle mouse button for this, actually.
It's much easier.
Not a single misclick so far.
Wonderful.
Let me actually have a look at this.
Let's see if I like it.
Don't blow up my shit!
Oh, man.
How did you get in here, anyway?
Hey!
Talking to you.
Don't you dare explode on me.
Whew!
Let's go to bed.
Dude, that is looking frickin' fantastic.
The problem is gonna be how to connect the rest here.
I think that's gonna be a real, uh...
You know, puzzle to solve.
But it's gonna be okay.
Oh, shit.
Put this in there.
So, wait.
How did I do this before?
Oh, I already made this part.
So, I guess I can just...
I can do this.
Bring it all the way over.
And then we do the same procedure.
Good.
Why didn't I do this earlier, man?
Remember when I made roof the very first time?
I would have been 10% of the way...
Compared to my, right now, 100%, you know?
If this is the baseline.
Oh, wait.
A little mouse click.
Dude, I actually have no problem making roofs.
I'm actually an expert.
Well, not an expert expert, but...
Professional.
Now the problem is, how am I gonna do this part?
Definitely, we wanna do it the other way.
Let me just start over here.
Keep it simple.
So, the way I did it was that.
And...
That's the same procedure I did over here, right?
And that one we did...
Yeah.
That is correct.
That is what I did.
And we wanna go...
One further.
Like that.
Wait.
Let me think.
Wait, how the hell am I gonna do this?
Don't think about it.
Just do it.
Enter a flow state where you don't use your brain.
Just fucking go with it.
It'll all make sense.
When we reach the end.
Oh.
This one needs to be...
Extended.
But not too much.
Actually, that's the right amount.
And one more.
Now we're consistent with the rest.
Ah, it looks a little...
I'm not sure.
Okay, fuck.
The question is, when do I stop here?
I guess I wanna stop halfway on this...
Actually, right here.
Is that halfway?
I'm looking at this beam here, right?
Yeah, that's halfway.
The question...
This is the big test.
How does it look when I come from this angle?
No, stop that.
How on earth is this gonna...
Wait, hold on.
Something's wrong.
Honestly, I like it, I think.
I don't like...
I don't like that.
Uh-oh.
Wait, we have a problem.
Or do we?
No, this is gonna be solid wall here.
This right here is gonna be...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
We're making a solid wall here.
Um...
Trust in the process.
It's gonna be good.
And even if it's not perfect...
You know?
I think that has a charm.
Like, if it's a little uneven, a little, uh, you know, ramshackle...
That's actually by design.
You know?
Cause it's made by an amateur, uh...
You know, woodcutter out in the forest.
He just put it together real quick, you know?
It has its charm.
That's the way you should think about it.
See, but now the problem is...
I don't know if I like this, guys.
I gotta be honest here.
Maybe just trust it.
Trust it'll be good.
But what about this roof?
Oh, no.
Oh, this is actually kind of a disaster.
Wait.
You know what, actually?
It's not too bad!
Because watch.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Stop, stop, stop.
Why is it not doing the angle thing?
Stop!
Yeah!
Look at that!
We are cooking!
Oh, that's beautiful!
Oops, I told you to trust the process here.
It's all gonna come together.
Oh, it even connects automatically.
That is wonderful.
Oops.
I need to be precise with my clicks here.
But see, now the problem is that we can't really connect in the same way.
But that's okay, that's okay!
Don't question it, just keep going.
Hey!
It still works!
But now it doesn't.
Or does it?
Ah, crap!
Oh no, we have a hole.
Maybe it's okay.
Damn it.
Wait, I'm actually happy with this.
Do I like that?
No, I don't like that.
This is gonna be...
We're gonna end up having...
Hmm.
Let me think.
I think just planks here.
This is solid, right?
This is the way to do it.
I just need to see the concept here.
Then we remove...
No, we don't actually.
We keep this.
Boom!
Oh, I'm stuck.
Honestly, I think that's good.
I'm happy.
Now we just gotta connect this all the way.
Well, that's an awkward angle.
How on earth...
This is a real mess here.
Dude, I'm happy.
I like it.
Remember, if it's inaccurate or, you know, not perfect, that's the whole charm.
That's the point.
It needs to be that way.
It's a little, you know...
Dude, that actually looks fucking sick.
I'm not gonna lie.
I kinda killed it there.
Whoa.
Man, it's very brown, isn't it?
We gotta...
We gotta add a little something something at the end here.
This is just the outline, you know?
The skeleton.
The template.
Dude, I need to see how this looks from a distance.
I wish I could fly.
I need elytra.
You know?
I actually like it!
I actually do.
Hold on, because we're not done.
It's gonna get better.
You'll see what I mean.
Like, for example, this.
We're gonna do stuff like this, right?
And here as well.
Look, it's gonna get much better.
Much better already.
And here.
Shit.
Fuck yeah!
Okay, this looks a little funky over there, but don't look at that.
That doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
Okay, let's start in the third one.
Two out of three done.
How do we wanna angle this one?
Dude, maybe we go for a flat one on the third.
Have like a little terrace, maybe?
Imagine that!
Or even- Oh!
Even better.
Garden of Turbulence 2.0.
I never got to finish my vision.
Tiny Garden of Turbulence.
Right?
T-G-O-T.
T-GOT.
We're doing T-GOT.
Ah, but I- There is one problem here.
I don't like that.
Why does it look like that?
I don't like this.
Maybe I can- Actually, we don't need to see- This can just go away.
Much better!
And then here?
Uh...
No.
No, how did I- Wait.
Fuck yeah!
Dude, I'm actually cooking right now.
Watch this.
We're gonna make a beam that goes across.
I'm totally freestyling.
Dude!
But now it's like, kinda...
Oh!
Solution!
We make the floor one deeper.
In fact...
We make it two deeper.
What do you say to that?
It's gonna be good.
That way we have more room to the- Like, space...
Upwards, you know?
Vertical space is what's that called.
I'm gonna get rid of this.
This is gonna be- Uh, let me think.
This is gonna end up being- Well, and the side stuff.
But, uh, we're gonna put in temporary...
Floor.
Actually, temporary floor is gonna be dirt.
So I'm just gonna remove one layer right now.
And then later on, we're gonna put in the other stuff.
Because I'm not gonna have enough andesite anyway.
Temporary dirt floor.
TDF.
TDF and T-GOT.
I also hate that I have this set up here, you know?
Where it's mix and match.
I'd rather just get rid of that.
But...
There is one problem.
Which is those bookshelves, right?
Uh, which is why we need...
Uh...
Silk touch!
And there is silk touch on that...
Enchanting table.
So we're gonna get that.
Before we do anything else.
Uh, well, I mean, before we remove those bookshelves.
That way we can save the...
Bookshelves, and it's gonna be genius.
Let me actually do the outline here.
Let me think.
If I want dirt up here...
I guess this is gonna have to be...
Not dirt.
Wait.
We need...
We actually need one more...
Hold on a minute.
Wait, what?
Hold on, something's wrong with this.
Oh, is that why it looked like that in there?
Ah, but you know what?
Actually, it doesn't matter.
Because this is gonna be dirt.
Dirt.
This is dirt.
Uh...
Get rid of this.
Here.
Dude, that's genius.
Dude, I actually...
I fucking nailed it.
Oh my god.
I'm amazing.
This is Teagot.
Uh...
But what about over here?
Fuck it!
We dirt all the way!
I need more dirt.
Dirt me!
Dude, I actually have the wildest vision right now.
I may have to readjust this later.
We'll have to see how it looks first.
Wait.
Hmm...
Actually, we can't have dirt in here, because that's gonna be visible.
Oh wait, this is just a beam I made, so...
We gotta keep it consistent.
Yeah.
Keep it consistent.
And if we go down too, we're gonna have more room for sealing, so we're just...
Yeah.
Actually, we're totally chilling.
And let me show you the vision here.
We're gonna connect it as if it's like a little hobbit place.
See that?
Something like that.
Maybe here.
Oh, I ran out.
But, you understand.
You get the idea.
It's gonna sort of flow down that way, you know, on this side.
Mmm!
So good.
Ah, but then the beam is gonna look like shit!
Unless I put the beam down...
Ah, but then it's not gonna be aligned.
Uh-oh!
I guess...
No, no, I understand...
Dude.
It doesn't matter.
You know why?
FJ.
That's why.
I got the FJs.
That's gonna make sure it looks good.
Also, nice that I get some wood back from destroying this.
We also have to remember, at some point we're gonna crash through the floor here and fall into a cave.
So we can't go deeper than this.
I think there's one more layer or maybe two layers.
Wait, I shouldn't have removed this.
Oh...
Wait a sec.
This was supposed to stay...
You know what?
Fuck it!
Fuck it.
You know what?
I'm gonna do a temporary nice-looking floor that is not entirely nice.
It is not 110% nice, but it's like 82% nice.
And we're gonna keep that for a while until we have the hotel in our bags and we have it, uh, you know, on the helicopter.
I'm not even sure I can do all that shit.
But we'll find out.
If not, I'm gonna make my own.
It doesn't matter.
I just have...
I can smell the vision.
Smell that?
Glory.
That's what that smells like.
God, it takes forever to remove this floor.
I should never have put it in, huh?
Why do I always end up doing this, you know?
I put in something and then I regret it later and change it.
I guess it's the iterative process.
It's quite normal.
I would argue, uh, iteration is the path to perfection.
You can't have something great without iterating on it.
Nobody starts out immediately having the best, you know?
I really wish I had efficiency on my axe though, I will say that.
Dude, maybe I even do the andesite casing now.
Even better, I just put down the...
Dude, I just realized how I'm gonna do it too.
I'm just gonna put down the stripped locks and then just walk around and apply it.
On the floor!
Oh my god.
Obviously.
So smart.
We're also gonna fix this, this is ugly.
Oops.
Oh, even better!
Dude!
The temporary 82% floor is just gonna be stripped wood!
And then when we have it, then we're gonna apply it!
Oh, wow.
That is so good!
Damn.
And it's gonna look decent, I guess.
Okay.
Floor is gone.
We got floating things.
That's very much a crime.
Get rid of it.
Uh, yeah.
Uh, chest can stay for now because, you know, it's annoying to empty it.
You know what?
Just for completeness sake.
We're gonna...
We're gonna fill this with normal wood as well.
Even though nobody's ever gonna see it.
It's gonna...
It's gonna make me calm in my mind.
Okay?
Maybe we go one further down.
No.
Stop while the getting is good.
Much better.
Oh, we're hitting stone!
I gotta be careful not to fall into a hole now and die.
And lose my experience, which is very much valuable to me.
Nice!
Let's take care of the walls now.
Even these.
And you know what?
We're gonna use this dirt to put on the roof!
It's perfect.
It's all coming together.
I spent way too long not finishing this house.
Today is the day it happens.
I'm gonna be so much more happy for it in the long run.
Look how clean this looks!
I'm gonna have to somehow fix a nice entrance here.
Because I see issues right now.
Look at that.
Mmm!
Beautiful!
And now...
We're gonna make the floor.
Temporary 82% floor coming up.
We may have to go crank it a little bit first.
Or maybe we don't.
No, we probably have to.
You know what?
Let's use this dirt while we have it.
Let's be proactive here.
This is not getting distracted, this is multitasking.
Let me see how I want this.
No!
Why are you not...
connecting?
Oh, there we go.
Beautiful.
Oh, that is actually so sexy looking!
Damn, I'm good.
I guess we are not gonna have a door here anymore.
Fill this up.
Let me actually just fill up these holes.
Any more holes?
I got a hole there.
Maybe I go even further here.
Let me see.
Oh, these need to go.
You know what?
Actually, this doesn't need to be here.
But, just for completeness sake.
I just don't...
I don't like this one.
In fact, I hate it.
Yeah, gimme!
Let's do this.
Let me just have a vision here.
Hold on.
Let me rub my temples.
Okay!
I see it.
Maybe we go like this.
Sort of.
See what I mean?
The idea is to make a little Hobbit style here.
Ah, but if this is gonna be covered, then I may as well fill it up now and then...
You know, wrap everything else around it.
So, if this is gonna be a thing, we're gonna have to do...
Probably something like this.
Oh, we're gonna need a lot of dirt for this one.
Let me see.
Yeah, it's looking not bad!
I like it!
In fact, we don't need...
We don't need this.
There we go.
And at the same time, we're emptying our inventory using this dirt.
I also don't want it to look too artificial here, so we gotta make some kind of...
gradient, you know?
Fuck this.
This is good.
I like showing a little bit here.
I can show a tiny bit.
You see the vision?
You see it, right?
Ran out of dirt.
So I'll come back later when I have more.
Oh, look at the way it sort of goes.
Oh, yeah!
Oh, it's so good.
I'm actually so proud of myself.
Okay, now!
We got...
Let's put this inside.
Put it in here.
In, in, in.
This is going over here.
Bow is equipped.
Saplings.
Doors.
We don't care about doors, do we?
We hate doors.
In.
One torch is pathetic.
Two torches is twice pathetic.
In with this.
Soul.
Sand.
No thanks.
What is in here?
Empty.
Okay.
It's time to crank it!
We're gonna go crank some shit.
There we go.
And a saw.
I may have the saw outside actually.
No, I saw it.
Get it?
CV, DC, CV, CV.
Let me get a boat.
I almost fell in the lava.
Dude, I'm gonna make a...
I'm gonna make a path here too.
Just like in the last season when I...
Remember the path I had?
I'm gonna make it this time, but better.
It's definitely very brown.
We may have to mix in some stone or something.
I think stone is a good mix with the brown.
It's a good contrast, you know?
I do like my stone.
I think stone looks good.
Where are the...
Thick trees?
I need the big boys.
Cause it doesn't really matter.
In the end, when you put the anticide thingy on it...
It doesn't matter which wood it is, you know?
Just check it out.
Wood.
Oh, wait.
Stripped.
Wait, and strip it with the...
With the press?
Oh!
Is that actually better?
For stripped...
Oh no, this is wood.
Nevermind, nevermind, nevermind.
Nevermind.
I'm losing my mind.
I should probably do strip...
Ah, here we go, here we go.
One dark oak becomes...
I mean, it's just easier to do this manually, I think.
For now at least.
At this scale we're working with, I think we're good.
You know?
It's alright.
Here we go, big boy trees!
Crank that shit!
Oh yeah!
Let's see how fast I can do this.
But I hate that it automatically fills my inventory.
That's bad.
CV.
Shit.
God, I love this thing so much!
That is just so nice.
You know?
CV.
Oh
yeah.
Yeah.
I may even have enough right now.
I think I do.
Well, let's do one more tree.
Let's do this one.
No, this one.
Crank it.
I love the way it sort of falls down like a tree, you know?
And it's all...
logical.
Okay, now we go north.
This should be north.
I didn't look, but I think it's north.
Yeah, birch trees.
Lake.
Yep.
Even have some pumpkins here.
I will say though, the pumpkins look nice.
Maybe I'll...
You know?
From fairy tales and shit, they have pumpkins all over.
Maybe I'll have a little stack of pumpkins next to my house.
I'll have a couple pumpkins.
It's gonna add some color, right?
To the otherwise very brownish look.
We're gonna make a little pumpkin stack.
Ah, look at my roof!
Is that my roof?
Oh, I missed it.
Hold on, is that my roof?
Shit!
Okay, hold on.
It's not my roof.
One of these days, the roof shall be mine.
Maybe I'll make it taller.
Maybe I'll make a tower inside the center.
Yo!
Imagine.
We have the elevator going down to the cave.
And we can get off in the middle, which is my house.
But you can also keep going up!
Into a tower.
And this time, I'm not gonna make a shitty tower like the one I did last time.
This time, it'll be a round tower.
No more square towers.
I learned my lesson.
That was just absolute dog shit, what I made.
It's gonna be good, man.
Oh, it's actually fantastic.
We don't need these saplings, though.
Throw them away.
We can even make pulp out of it.
Hmm.
Should I?
Should I make pulp?
No.
Let's just start with this.
Here comes the floor!
Uh-oh.
Honestly, I even like this floor.
This floor is kind of nice, just on its own.
Even without stripping.
But obviously, stripping is gonna take it from 57% to 82%.
And then actually putting on the andesite is gonna take it to 110.
So you want those last percentages, obviously.
Notice how I'm using the grain going this way.
I guess it doesn't matter when I put on the andesite stuff.
It's not gonna matter which direction the grain is going.
And who knows, maybe I'll love this floor so much, I don't even wanna put the thing on.
Yeah, no, I hate this floor.
We're gonna have to strip that.
Yeah, better.
Not great, but better.
I like the sound when you're stripped.
Dude, wait a sec.
I kinda like the way it looks when it's like half-stripped, half-not-stripped.
Look at it!
I mean, it's not bad, but you know, it's an idea for later.
If we wanna do something like that.
I'm saying there are options, you know, we can make different looking things here.
By half-stripping.
We don't take all of it off, you know.
We keep some of it on.
That way, uh, fantasy takes over as well.
Fantasy is the strongest drug.
So, really, what I should be doing is just not make a house and just have you guys imagine.
A beautiful house.
Right?
Hells yeah.
That looks pretty decent.
And maybe I even put it in some of this.
Ugly!
Put it here.
Wait...
Maybe...
I level this floor a little bit.
Cause I actually kinda hate having a staircase going down.
Feels like a basement.
We're gonna level this just slightly outside the door.
You'll see what I mean.
It's gonna make sense.
Right?
And then...
We're gonna do this.
Not bad.
Okay.
This one's gonna be changed to this too.
Beautiful.
And now we do...
That...
Oh yeah!
And then door on the inside.
You ready?
Fuck yeah!
Windows obviously are coming.
Now the roof here is...
Don't look at the roof.
Don't look at that yet.
It ain't done.
There's plants.
I need to make torches.
I need sticks and coal.
I have it nice.
I'm gonna make sticks out of this.
27.
Wow, that's almost perfect.
Look at that.
Put this in here and keep that there.
Uh...
Let's actually connect these fully.
I think that could look really nice.
Look at that.
We could even...
Oh yeah, dude!
Look at this!
Dude, tell me I'm not cooking!
Uh...
One, two...
Huh?
Not bad.
And then here...
We're even gonna have a pillar.
Maybe two of them.
Hm?
Ah, okay.
Maybe just one.
Yeah.
Maybe this one also.
Going across...
I need more.
Dude, this is looking sick!
This is not looking very sick.
I will say...
I will say that.
I admit it.
We can fix it though.
I mean, I was gonna do this anyway, right?
So...
And then I can use these beams to walk on.
It's beautiful.
Except...
This one, I wanna keep clean.
To fill up with blocks, right?
Oh.
Whoops.
Ah, I can't get that again.
Ah, but you know what?
Check this out.
We're gonna use the handlebar.
God
tell me that's not amazing!
Whoa!
So useful.
Wow.
That's looking wrong.
Also wrong.
Man, I ran out of stairs?
That's crazy.
Go to bed.
Cheers.
Let me do this.
Ha ha ha ha!
I love that thing!
Oh, I forgot to make my stairs.
Stairs.
Stair me.
Let's make it a little bit.
Not too much.
A stack.
Oh,
also...
Ah, wait.
I don't actually like what I'm doing here.
Why does it look different?
Oh, it's because of this?
Get that out of there.
And then that stays.
And then...
Now we're good.
That looks...
Yeah, that's good.
And here come the big blocks.
I may have to turn this into stone.
We'll see.
I just don't like that this is not perfectly aligned here, but it's okay.
You don't notice that anyway.
Maybe I'd rather just fill this up like this here.
Does that look better than that?
Let me think.
Let
me think.
I think so.
I think it's better.
Oh, shit.
No.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Come on.
Up we go.
Oh, please.
Can I...
There we go.
And then we remove these.
Wait, I need to kill that Enderman.
Don't go anywhere.
I need you.
Hey, dude.
I heard him over here.
Enderman?
Oh.
Where are you?
Hello?
Are you inside?
Oh, shit.
Uh.
Hey, man.
Come here.
Oh.
Come on.
Nice.
We got a pearl.
Huge.
Like that.
Yeah, okay.
Now it kind of looks weird.
Doesn't that look weird?
No, it looks good.
I'm happy.
It is beautiful.
What the fuck just happened?
Oh, did I just use the pearl?
Oh, man.
I thought I got attacked.
Jesus.
Holy crap.
That got me good.
Sounded exactly like an Enderman just teleported into me and started messing with me.
See that?
Oh, it's looking good.
Oh, that's good.
But why is this weird?
Weird.
It's not weird.
It's actually good.
Beautiful.
Wow.
That is just immaculate.
Whoa, that was a...
Whoa, I'm getting sick.
Oh, shit.
Oh, look at this.
Wow.
The fuck?
That's crazy.
All right.
What now?
So we have some dirt here, which is not great, but I have an idea.
Okay?
Flapjacks.
That's the secret.
Wait, wait.
Fuck.
What is the real word?
I keep forgetting.
It is trapdoor.
I'm gonna use these.
Nothing to see here.
In fact, it even looks good.
Fuckin' hell, that looks good.
I'm actually a genius.
Give me more wood.
Uh, trap.
I ain't with that trap, bull.
Let me put it this way.
I'm trying to get my ass back home.
You know what?
I kinda like this so much, I kinda wanna extend it.
But maybe only to here.
Let's dirt it up!
I like the dirt!
The dirt trap.
Ahoy!
Ahoy, matey!
Are you feeling the vibes?
I'm really feeling this groove.
You play by the heart?
I'm modest.
Alright!
I think it's time we go get that level.
So we can get, uh...
Enchanting.
I was about to say Silk Song.
But no, it's called...
Silk...
It's called...
Silk Touch!
So we need a shield.
It's not a shield.
We already got gold.
We do not need these goggles, actually.
Not right now.
They look fancy, but that's all they're good for.
Let's bring a bow.
We'd love to get more power on that bow.
I actually have 64 andesite alloys.
We could totally make a floor here.
But I don't think 64 is enough.
I think we need like 200.
Would be my guesstimate on this floor here.
But who knows?
Actually, you know what?
I kinda like this floor already.
As it is.
Yeah?
We definitely need some more food.
Let's fill this up.
Sand.
Pumpkins.
Haunted Bell is definitely a specialty weird item.
So let's put it in here.
Actually, no.
It's more like a really weird item.
So I'm gonna put it in here.
We don't need the crank or the saw right now.
Apples and seeds.
Don't need those.
This axe is about to expire as well.
Okay.
Are we ready?
Food check.
We got...
Maybe I should make a new axe.
Before we move on here.
Just a bag up, you know?
Yeah.
This is good.
I'm ready.
We're gonna take a quick trip to the nether.
Get level 30.
And then we're gonna get silksong.
Look at the progress I've made in no time.
Hey guys!
I'm back!
Ready to...
Wreck shit up.
Omega...
Oh!
Wait, I thought we're... we are friends.
We're friends.
Why is...
Oh wait, I need at least one arrow.
Otherwise infinity don't work.
Whoops.
I made a mistake.
A classic mistake.
Happens to the best of us.
Oh, I'm liking that house right now.
Guys.
I don't like this beam that we have going on there.
Why does it look like that?
We'll see about that.
Now I need one arrow.
Just one.
I think we could have put the portal a little closer.
I forgot how far away you have to be for the sounds to go away.
Okay.
Here we go.
I'm gonna go...
Down?
No.
Let's head this way.
Oh yeah?
Aw, come on!
Asshole!
There it is.
Aw, he dodged it!
Bastard!
Wow!
I tried.
Oh yeah, this was the spot with almost no experience.
Love having infinite arrows.
Oh, there's a lot down there.
But getting up again is a little annoying.
Ah, it's okay.
We'll figure it out.
Hey, we got endermen here!
Maybe it's time to kill them?
Uh, let's go down.
A little bit here.
Okay, now.
Come at me.
Tell me they can get up here.
Come on!
Really?
Wait.
Am I immune to standing here?
Oh shit!
Kill him fast!
Dude, I just discovered the ultimate technique.
Hey!
Come on!
There we go.
Did I even get any pearls?
No.
I honestly feel safer in the nether than I do in the real world.
You know why?
Because there's no creepers.
I can just pop up behind you and fuck your shit up.
Almost 30!
Oh, this was fast!
Oh, wow!
Already!
Why did I jump over the sea?
That, that...
If I fell down there, my life would have been in ruins.
It would have ruined my entire day.
Too risky with it.
Now we gotta get up here.
That way we have an easy path back.
Nah, I'm not gonna kill it.
If I'm not collecting experience or the tears...
What's the point, right?
I heard a bouncy boy.
Okay, I really hope...
Oh!
What are you doing here?
I really hope that my...
Silk touch...
Is still gonna be here.
And it's not something that disappears when you log out and log back in, you know?
Since last session.
I hope it's the same.
We're about to find out.
And...oh no!
I need one more diamond!
Okay.
Quick trip to...
The mines.
Before we go home.
One more trip.
I gotta get one more diamond.
Dude, what?
There we go.
Make it safe.
There's gotta be a diamond in here that I missed.
Just one.
It should be deeper, I guess.
Wait, what even is this place?
Creepers.
One diamond!
Come on.
That's all I need.
This was a very roundabout way of getting here.
Wait, fine.
Oh!
What if I died?
Imagine.
I wouldn't be too...
Yo, it would be too bad because I lost all my levels then.
Another Enderman!
Yo!
I'm so lucky right now.
Let's kill him.
Diamonds!
Oh, this is perfect.
Hey!
How's it hanging?
Come on, give me a pearl.
Boom!
Well, we got the diamonds.
Let's get out.
Oh, wait, can I even...
Watch this.
Oh, no, wait.
It's not gonna work.
I'll take another elevator.
Do you get pushed off the elevator?
When you get hit?
I didn't know that.
That's new information for me.
Uh...
I think up there?
Wait, how...
Wait, what...
Where am I?
Get up here.
I always get so lost.
Oh, there it is.
I was in the right place.
Now we just gotta get up.
And there's water there.
Beautiful.
Everything's starting to look up.
Oh, no.
Smart.
Yeah!
There's a cow.
What's up, cow?
Thanks.
I feel like these guys are breeding.
Out here.
Unchecked.
Okay, are you ready?
Here we go!
Axe!
This is the moment.
The moment of truth.
Are we gonna...
Where the hell is my...
There.
Are we gonna have silk touch?
Yes or no?
I say...
Yes.
Here we go.
Fuck yeah, I'm good.
An efficiency four, baby!
That is amazing!
Go to bed.
That is the best I could have hoped for.
Well, almost the best.
Pretty good.
So now I can safely do this?
It's all coming together here.
I'm also thinking of all the other possibilities now that I have silk touch.
Okay, so I guess I'm gonna put them in the same spot for now.
Why not?
No.
This one I relocate.
I'm gonna do a half here and then full there.
Maybe even like this.
Hey, that looks super good!
At least for now.
Then we're gonna...
I'm gonna fix this immediately, I think.
Just to get it over with.
Getting it over with.
Let's put the brewing thing...
here.
Chest.
Oh, I didn't get the chest.
Let's have that...
No, I don't like that actually.
Put this over here.
Nice!
Look at this, it's starting to look like something.
I'm gonna do the same with this thing.
Why are they...
Oh, is it jumping because of the spring?
Did you see that?
That was funny.
There we go!
Man, it feels good to be a gangster.
Hells yeah.
I'm actually not even finished with that.
I see more opportunities for beams.
Sea beams, in fact.
Glittering in the darkness.
Near the Tenhouser gate.
Where did I put mine?
Do I really have to go crank again?
Hmm.
So soon?
That's not right.
Fine.
I'll do it.
I knew I should have gotten more.
When I was there, you know?
But I was too excited.
I also got to go collect more beesaws.
I think by now, they should have produced.
What's up, dude?
I always see this black sheep whenever I come...
to crank, you know?
Let me crank in this direction.
I've been cranking so much over here.
Gotta switch it up a little bit.
Oh, wait!
I misremembered.
Am I gonna optimize this?
Watch.
I'm gonna do multiple at a time, and then we're gonna collect it all at the end.
Is that all?
Oh, this one's ugly.
Why is it ugly?
There's like no tree on the tree.
What happened?
Let's do...
a couple more.
Crank that shit.
I think some fell on the mushroom.
But it's okay.
What's my... oh.
Wait, something's off.
Yeah.
Huh.
That was a weird one.
That should do it.
Don't need no more than that.
That's why.
We go a little west as well as the northwest, because I went southeast.
Dude, I'm imagining a track...
across a bridge...
over this lake.
Instead of having to boat every time, you know?
I need to cross here.
Imagine that.
I have so many ideas for this location, actually.
I think today's the day I make the elevator.
Or at least try to.
Okay, so here...
What did I see that I... oh, here.
Dude, yes.
Yes!
Look at that!
It's wonderful.
Maybe we can do without that pillar.
We'll have to see.
Obviously, this is kind of temporary, where I've put this stuff.
You know, it's a little temporary.
Not fully, but kinda.
Putting some proper lights down.
Light down the pillar.
Light here.
One there.
There.
That one.
Nice.
Oh!
Let's put that in the center.
There we go.
Look at that!
Mmm!
Nice.
Starting to feel like home.
Compared to what I had when I started?
I mean...
Frickin' look at that.
Ah, this one is annoying.
Needs to be fixed.
That way.
Better.
Oh!
You know what?
This door is not centered.
What if we make two doors?
The frickin' script writes itself right now.
The other door.
Put that in there.
Other apples.
Beef.
Ah, we can cook the beef.
Oh, right.
I was cooking this as well.
In the charcoal.
Let's put this, uh, dried kelp in here.
We're gonna work with that later.
Another quartz goes in here.
We can also blast this.
Uh, I can't wait for this axe to be done so I can start a new one.
Uh, this diamond pickaxe.
Let's put it in here for now.
Oh, I need to take off this.
There we go.
I got the door.
Dude, that is wonderful.
Except, I don't know if I like this.
Maybe I'll...
Hmm.
I guess this needs to be grass.
Or dirt.
Whatever.
Because then we put...
the doors on the inside.
Better.
In fact, this is gonna be stone later.
We're gonna make a stone path.
Obviously.
Yes, yes.
Dude, I am actually so happy about this roof here.
I mean, look at this!
Doesn't that look like a rich man's mansion or something?
We sit in a couch over here.
With a cognac in our hand and a cigar in the other, you know?
And then we have our frickin' factory out here later.
That's gonna pollute the shit out of it.
The whole nature, we're gonna, you know, pollute into the lake.
We're gonna pollute everywhere.
Hmm.
Yeah.
I'm not done with that roof.
Need some more...
stairs.
Maybe it's time to bring all this inside.
What do you say?
Can't be sleeping in the damn rain.
Where do we sleep?
Maybe we sleep next...
We sleep here for now.
What do we blast?
Here?
I like that.
Yep.
We will even bring this in.
And get rid of this now.
These are gonna stay a little longer.
Much better.
Okay, so, stairs.
Um...
This is gonna be...
This...
Let me finish this first.
Nice.
I like the way that looks.
I can't reach.
Wait.
I think I wanna do this, actually.
On that side.
Yeah, this is...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here.
This is gonna be blocked off, of course.
That's wrong.
Correct.
No, it's wrong.
Yeah.
Can you feel it?
Oh, it's so sexy.
We actually don't need this dirt here.
Instead, we're gonna use...
Uhm...
Oh, yeah.
Wait.
Am I...
No, it's good.
It's good.
This is wrong.
Wait!
It's not wrong!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's fine.
This is correct.
Abort, abort!
There we go!
That's more like it.
Why is my screen so...
Nice!
Nice, oh yeah.
And then what did I do?
Wait, something's wrong here.
Oh, this, oh.
We don't need this, actually.
I was a little premature on that one.
But do we need this dirt?
We don't need this dirt.
Dude, it's perfect!
Look at it, man!
I'm even gonna do this.
We're gonna connect it, like, here.
Oh, yeah.
Look at how aligned it is.
It's beautiful.
It's wonderful.
Mmm.
This house is sexy.
You ready for the next step?
Watch this.
Oak saplings.
Right?
We're gonna have birch saplings.
We're not done.
Bonemeal.
We're gonna go on this roof.
And it's raining.
The seeds are gonna grow.
Something like this.
You see that?
Look how pretty that is.
Now we make them grow.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Actually, that's good.
Grass it up, too.
Full grass.
Grow, motherfucker.
I want to see you grow.
Yeah.
Look how grassy it is.
It's coming together.
More.
It's too much.
Too much green.
Cut down on the green.
Slightly.
It also... I also don't want people to think I don't maintain my garden, right?
Like, it is turbulent, but it's not that turbulent.
Let's have another tree here.
Whoops.
Maybe one here.
Fucking look at that.
Isn't that...
pretty.
We're done with this here.
Don't eat this.
Not right now, at least.
Wait, I forgot how this works.
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
There we go.
I have done it.
Clean it up.
Not that one.
That's it.
Oh, man.
It's beautiful.
I'm actually going to change this, too.
Oh!
Look!
How pretty.
Oh, my God!
It's good!
Guys.
I feel like I've become a master.
This is just too amazing.
Look at that roof right there.
Look at this roof.
The way it all connects.
We have flat roof here with grass and greenery on top.
Oh, yeah.
And now...
I think it's time we go to sleep.
Okay.
I need food.
Maybe it's time for the elevator.
We need to figure out how that even works.
Put all this in here.
Running out of space.
Oh, I ran out of space.
Damn.
What do we not need in here?
Fuck this gravel.
This one we don't need.
We don't need this.
Or that.
Throw it away.
Into the fire.
You know, I'm tempted to just move these boxes right now.
Move them inside, you know?
Get it over with.
I think I'm going to do it.
But for that to happen, I do need to ready my inventory a little bit here.
This is going to be for transfer.
Eh, good enough.
Let's fill it up.
A telephone?
That goes in here.
Wait, am I hearing a bee outside?
What the fuck?
The bees have made a home!
The hell?
Why?
Why is that?
That's weird.
I guess I can collect that later.
I'm going to be annoyed with the sound, so...
Oh, wait, I've got silk touch!
I'm going to safely relocate you.
That's right.
Look at this.
Come with me.
You're going to go over here now.
That's your home.
What was I going to need now?
The door here.
Maybe two doors.
I have one door left.
May as well use it.
Put that here.
Oh, wait.
What about I'll...
Wait a second.
I forgot I made my whole top part transferable.
This is all going in there.
That makes more sense now.
Same as that one.
This axe is going to break now.
Hopefully.
I may make a little space in between.
Just like I did in that other place.
But then it's not really...
That's okay.
Next.
Dude, are you proud of me?
Look at this.
I'm finally cleaning up here.
It's not taking me ten years.
Oh, no.
I didn't get the...
Oh, I hate when that happens.
You know what?
Maybe I'll do...
Two, two, two...
Oh, actually, yeah.
Yeah.
We're going to do that.
We're going to relocate this bastard.
A second here.
Damn.
I didn't get the...
I'll put all of this in here.
Grab the last one.
It all goes in this box.
Now, um...
I guess I could move this wall a little bit.
So...
I could also move this wall a little bit.
I mean, it's going to be dirt.
Who cares?
Nobody will know.
Let me think.
Yeah.
We're going to have to move this over one.
It is what it is.
This needs to be perfect from the start.
Oh, that's right.
That breaks.
Where's my other one?
Axe.
This is actually so fortunate, you know?
This is the place where we don't have the angled roof.
Otherwise, we would have to redo the roof.
And that's no bueno.
But right now, it's very bueno.
We like it right now.
Really?
I'm missing one?
That's crazy.
Really?
Oh, wait.
I can take it here.
This needs to change anyway.
Let's go get the last locks.
Much better.
And now, we extend this wall one more that way, too.
And then...
Then this area is complete.
I'm so glad I didn't make a roof on this side.
I'm like an angled roof.
So, I guess this is going to be...
Planks now.
I guess we'll get rid of this tree.
It's ugly anyway.
Beautiful.
And now, we change this out again.
Be the pillar.
And I guess this one will have to change.
Because we've got to align them with the corner, right?
That's the whole point.
Let's eat some food.
Where's my food?
Good enough.
This one needs to be extended.
Yes!
That's it.
Maybe not.
Actually, yes.
Oh, that is...
Oh, that's beautiful.
Oh, yes.
Dude, it's all coming together here.
And now, we have room for exactly what I was envisioning here.
Because I'm going to have a little separation going on.
I'll show you.
This is like my standard setup, you know?
Two chests.
And so on and so forth.
A little dark in here.
I make it here.
And we have one in the corner, too.
Maybe up here we can sort of connect.
I'm totally freestyling this right now.
This could turn out to be really bad looking.
Let's see.
So far?
I mean, look at that!
Come on!
That looks cool.
And then we're going to put this in here.
Dirt.
Like that.
Where do I put the wood?
For now.
Let's put it in...
This one.
Simple rarely.
Okay.
Let's transfer this over.
Hey, you know what would be useful here?
If you had that item that automatically...
Puts everything in.
You know the one I had in the very first world?
That could be useful.
Forgot what it's called.
Yes!
Look!
Tell me that isn't...
Spectacular.
I'm actually so happy.
We're finally making some good progress here.
The only thing I don't like too much...
We may have to do this beam here.
Instead of this, we're going to put a beam.
Just to be a little...
Consistent with the other side.
The only problem is...
It's going to look funky here.
Because it's going to...
Ah, it's fine.
Honestly, looks good.
I'm happy.
Yep.
That's cool.
Very nice.
We can put in more chests too, if we want to.
In fact, let's put down the tables again.
Maybe not here.
This is going to be chest area.
Maybe we have a little thing in the center.
Like a little...
Imagine a kitchen island.
But instead of a kitchen, it's...
Well, it is kind of a kitchen, I guess.
You know?
Dude, that's sick!
And then chests all around?
Yeah!
Come on.
Tell me that isn't awesome.
In fact, I'm going to make something like this here.
You see that?
We're going to put a wooden bracket on it too.
If I can, I can't.
Okay, whatever.
I don't like that.
Maybe I do this.
Flap it down.
Flippy flap.
Oh, no, no, no.
Even better.
Let's put the little table cover thingy on.
And a side table cover.
Yeah!
Cardboard!
Right there!
We're going to have some brackets sitting.
Mmm, look at that.
I like it.
Oh, wait, whoa!
This needs to change.
Wrong.
Actually, yeah, whatever.
That was actually a mistake.
But it's okay.
That's more like it!
Yeah!
Oh, ho, ho!
Okay.
I think over here, we may also have to do this sort of maneuver.
Just to keep it consistent, you know?
Mmm.
I like it.
I'm so excited.
Oh, my God.
Let's bring the last chest over.
But first...
Empty inventory.
Hmm.
Uh, give me the meat.
That's...
Now we grab the last chest.
We're pro- Like, I am...
I feel like I've taken the pill from Limitless.
You know what I mean?
And I see clearly now.
Now I can focus on things.
Where are those chests at?
That I just got.
Oh.
The question is, if I put it here, we can still open, right?
Yes.
Good.
Now the organization and where we put items are obviously going to change over time.
This is just temporary.
I actually heard that people who have severe ADHD, when they finally get their medicine for the first time, it's like getting the Limitless pill.
That's why I would love to try it.
To get the pill, I mean.
Wait a sec.
I actually have an even better idea.
Maybe I'm going too crazy with this, but check it out.
Hear me out.
Now I need more wood.
Now watch.
We're going to extend these pillars down.
Yeah, that's...
Yeah, that's fine.
Eh!
You know what?
I'm 50-50 on that one.
I'm not entirely happy.
I'm not entirely unhappy.
Definitely need some kind of window on the side.
And maybe that becomes stone, you know?
Oh, wait.
Wait.
Maybe one side is stone.
And the other is wood.
We make a mix.
Also, we got to empty these pockets.
What do I need here?
Very soon.
What will I need?
Maybe steaks.
Oh, uh...
Bucket.
Bucket, bucket, bucket.
It's got to be here somewhere.
I think I have another bucket.
But, whatever.
I'm going to empty this here.
You know what?
Let's put this one here instead.
Yeah!
Oh, my God.
I don't know why I have cardboard here.
I just do.
I like displaying my cardboard.
Just like real life.
That's why I have three full tables at my home.
With, like, cardboard decorations on it, you know?
I mean, not just, like, flat cardboard.
It's, like, actually...
People and animals and stuff, you know?
So, yeah.
I'm kidding, by the way.
I don't have that at home.
But I would love to have it.
It sounds cool.
Basically, I'm describing how I want to be.
Okay, you ready for the next step?
Watch this.
We're going to grab stone.
Okay?
Cobblestone.
Uh...
Oh, wait, wait.
Now that we have...
Uh...
Silk Touch.
We could actually do some funky things.
How do I make the...
Um...
Stony thingies?
Oh, this one.
Stone breaks.
Oh, I need stone.
Okay.
And to get stone...
I have to cook things, I believe.
So in here...
Give me my coal.
I think I just need to do this, if I'm not mistaken.
Oh, yeah.
It even says so.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it's going to take a while.
But so...
Hold on a minute.
So stone...
Let me see here.
Stone breaks.
I think I can do it like that.
Oh, yeah.
I can also blast in bulk.
Guys, wait a minute.
Am I crazy?
Or...
Is this...
Infinite...
Blasting?
This is not going to run out.
Wait, did I just discover a fucking...
Crazy method here?
Wait.
Infested stone.
I don't want to make infested stone.
That sounds glitchy.
Hmm.
How do I make just normal stone again?
Right, cobblestone.
Okay.
And smooth stone.
Right.
The problem with this is I can't retrieve the items without diamonds.
Dying.
So I got to devise a method to not die.
And I guess it would be a hopper?
Hopper on the spot where they land...
Oh, but wait.
They're going to be absorbed immediately.
How am I going to make sure that doesn't happen?
Maybe I can...
Oh, I know there's something like filters now.
So maybe I can put a hopper or a chute or something.
Just with the filter of the cooked item.
So that the uncooked items don't fall through.
Right?
And they only get absorbed.
Or sucked in.
When it's the...
The cooked item.
Or the output item.
Right?
I guess.
You know what I mean.
Also, what the...
I can make those...
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Right.
Makes sense.
Oh, yeah.
What did I discover in here?
The deployer?
I gotta try that today.
I actually kind of do.
Thrust producing blocks.
Components which produce thrust on simulated contraptions.
Nozzle.
Wait, that produces thrust?
Attached to the front of an encased fan to distribute its effect on entities in all directions.
Oh, okay.
All right.
So it's definitely like a fan type item.
Throttle lever.
What is that one?
Throttle levers make for a compact and precise something.
I didn't get to read it.
Right click and drag to set its analog power output.
But how is this different from the analog lever?
Isn't that the same thing that does?
Using a wrench, the signal can be inverted.
Inverted?
What do you mean inverted?
What?
Okay.
That's fine.
Bar of chocolate.
Wait.
Should I make...
Hold on.
Chocolate.
How the hell do I make chocolate?
250 millibars of chocolate, maybe?
I don't know.
What the hell?
Whatever.
I feel like it's a little too full.
Like, it's kind of empty.
Not full.
It's like open and it needs to be more dense.
I need something in the center.
Maybe it is more pillars.
Or I section it off with rooms.
Maybe I should do that, actually.
It's one big room right now, and I'm not a big fan of that.
Give me wood.
I could section it off here.
Or even here.
With a door.
Oh, actually.
I like that, I think.
I'm just going to experiment.
I have no idea how this is going to look.
We'll see.
It's going to be terrible.
Who knows?
Who cares?
Bring a little opening into here.
Hey, I actually kind of like that.
Not bad.
Let's make one here, too.
Yo!
Man, this did so much!
Right?
I feel like this did so much.
This I don't like, though.
We need to somehow combine this.
In a nice way.
I guess we can make it like that.
Let me try.
Yo, wait.
Hold on, I'm cooking.
I kind of like this entrance!
Look at it!
Wait.
We need flabby jaggies.
Flap my jacks.
Oh, wait.
We gotta do this, of course.
Wait, what's happened there?
Alert, alert!
What the fuck?
Wait, something's wrong here.
Oh, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
Yeah.
Right.
Yeah, yeah.
There we go.
And then...
Flap.
This is the...
Flapjack room.
You know why?
Flapjack's on the roof.
That's why.
What do you think?
Not bad, eh?
This is gonna be...
These types...
Oh, wait.
No, no, no.
Hold on.
Put it back.
We need a door.
We need doors.
Doors, doors.
Do!
Door.
Oh, wait, wait.
Wait a minute.
Watch this.
Wait.
Something's off.
It's like a saloon!
Dude, that actually looks sick!
Tell me that isn't actually amazing.
Look at this entrance to the chest room!
Mmm!
Huh?
Not bad.
And you know what?
We're gonna make it better.
I'm not done.
Yeah, I'm done.
I think I'm done.
I'm not done!
I'm not done yet.
Jackie, get off the table!
Jackie, you cannot be on the table right now.
I'm making...
Saloon entrance.
And then?
Fuck yeah!
Wait.
Oh.
Hold on.
We got issues.
That's it!
Wait!
Hold on.
I'm not done.
Jackie, get off!
Okay.
Come here.
You're spreading hairs everywhere.
I feel like I may have overcooked a little here.
The food is getting a little stale.
Ah, it ain't good.
I feel like this is a little too much.
Yo!
Keep it simple!
This...
Jackie.
Come here.
This is where the rotating door is gonna be!
Hey, Jackie.
Are you impressed with my constructions?
Hmm?
Look at it.
You like it?
Don't...
Don't rub...
Okay, fine.
My mic is gonna be filled with cat hair.
Good thing I have a...
A hair roller.
No, come here.
Guys, I hate it.
I have...
I mean, it's not bad, but...
I feel like I haven't reached my full power.
I can do better.
We're not done.
There's something else we can do.
I need to think on it.
What if...
I have an idea.
No, I did...
No, bad idea, bad idea.
Actually, yes!
Wait.
I have a better idea.
Ay, what about that, huh?
We make it just open.
Huh?
I like that.
That's nice.
But then we're gonna complete this, because it's part of the room.
Ah!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hold on.
That's not quite working, is it?
Let's leave it at that.
Why am I even doing this?
Oh, this doesn't even make any sense.
We don't even need this here.
Can I not just...
Wait.
Can I not just do this?
Oh, I see.
But maybe we angle it.
And then this one's gonna go like that.
Oh!
Actually, I'm not feeling...
It's not quite my tempo.
That's fine.
Eh, it is what it is.
It's okay.
We gotta stop at some point, you know?
Otherwise, it's getting a little too crazy.
Okay, let me see what we have in terms of windows here.
Whoops.
Oh!
No.
Huh.
I put my pickaxe on the table.
Window.
Wait, we actually have a couple different ones.
Ornate iron windows.
Birch.
We gotta make dark oak windows.
It's just glass and planks.
Glass and planks.
I got it.
Oh, we unlocked something new now.
Ah, window pane.
Mmm.
Let me make some.
Wait, I can blast that?
What are you saying?
Oh.
I can wash the...
Wait, is there like a dirtiness mechanic?
How the hell does that work?
I can wash my windows.
Huh.
Okay.
What the hell is that?
Whoa.
Engine assembly.
Cut with saw.
Process and press.
Dude, we need belts.
This is like belt territory.
Whoa.
Gyroscopic mechanism.
Okay, bro.
Calm down.
That's a little outside my pay grade right now.
I'm not gonna lie.
That's too much.
I can barely understand...
Flapjack doors.
Man, I don't like...
I don't...
Mmm.
That's okay.
Oh, actually, I have another idea here.
Ideas of forming.
You wanna see something crazy?
Watch this.
I just had a really good idea.
But we're gonna need oak for this.
Oh, I don't have a lot.
Yikes.
Okay.
I guess that's not happening then.
Not right now.
I was gonna make some oak flapjacks.
Wait, why does that oak look like that?
That's wrong.
That's more like it.
Yeah.
Good, good, good, good, good.
Then we had another door.
Nice.
And then we have windows.
Maybe we can...
Oh, we got bookshelves here.
Never mind.
I mean, I can rotate the bookshelves.
Would be nice to have a window on each side, right?
What about here?
Oh, okay.
What does it even look like?
That's kinda cute.
I kinda wanna make it bigger.
I don't...
I think this is all gonna be dirt over here.
Which is perfect because we have storage here.
We don't need windows anyway.
Right?
Make a big window.
Whoa!
Wait, look at that!
It's like extending vertically.
Dude, that looks sick!
Oh, that's dirt.
Okay, I was gonna take it all the way down.
That's too much, maybe.
Okay, let's leave it at that for now.
Let me put some windows here.
And I think we may need two doors here as well.
This needs to be dirt.
Watch this.
Man, that actually looks kinda sick!
I like that!
I don't like that.
But if I rotate it the other way, then we can see it here.
Hmm, that's a conundrum.
Not a conundrum I'm particularly happy about.
I guess I can extend this out, maybe?
Not with that.
But it's good to get some light in here.
This is all gonna be dirt, right?
Let me see.
Not quite.
Almost.
We can go one further down here.
There we go.
Shit.
Oh, no.
Hells yeah!
Dude, yes.
Oh, my God.
So, obviously, this is not great here.
But, uh, we're gonna move these to somewhere else.
Uh,
windows.
Not bad.
Well, kinda bad.
But not super bad.
Yo, what if I went crazy?
Full window.
That actually looks kinda nuts.
But in the best way, you know?
I don't like this part here.
So, maybe we...
Oh, God.
How do I handle that?
Maybe this?
Oh, no!
It looks weird!
I could just extend it here.
Yeah.
We extend the illusion.
Cover this up.
Beautiful!
That's it, baby.
We're gonna have flowers out here, too!
In fact, we can do the same thing out here.
Dude, I like these windows a lot.
Let me see how that looks from inside.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Oh, yes!
This is dirt, right?
Yeah, it is dirt.
This is gonna be a window.
It's not, I guess.
I shall make it so.
We don't need dirt out here.
In fact, I'm gonna make a little place out here where I drink my coffee and read the newspaper.
In the morning.
We'll see what I mean in a sec.
I have a great idea.
I'm gonna need some planks.
Yeah, give me some fence, I guess.
And some trap doors.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Give me everything.
Give me all you got.
Oh, I got more dirt here, too.
Nice.
Maybe I'll even make some slaps.
I know, right?
Let's finish this window.
This is a big window.
It's a glorious window.
Oh, my God!
It looks so good!
Oh, my goodness!
Let me see how I want to do this.
So, this is gonna be like a little outside area.
A little entrance here.
It could even be there and then move that.
Yeah, actually.
This is the door.
Better.
Now, watch this.
Maybe something like...
Oh, my God!
Look at this!
What?
Why is it floating?
No!
I don't like that.
Maybe a slab.
Time out!
We're gonna slab it instead.
Nope.
What if I slab here?
Can I connect that somehow?
Maybe I need to put it higher.
Oh, wait a minute!
No, lower.
Yeah!
Oh, yeah.
That's it.
That is totally it.
Actually, maybe I connect that to...
Wait, I got a better idea.
Let's go a little more crazy.
All the way to here.
Get this tree out of my face!
Let's do one more.
And connect it!
And now?
Nope.
Wrong.
Maybe it's still a little too brown here, but, you know.
But it...
Oh, you know what I need?
I need oak trapdoors.
With the little holes in them so I can see through.
That's what I need.
But I could also...
Man, why is it floating?
I hate that.
Boo!
I mean, this is what I have right now.
Maybe I'll alternate a little bit here.
Something like that.
You see the vision?
Maybe we connect like this now?
Oh, my God.
Why are you not...
Why are you no-connect?
It's fucking slaps, dude.
Again.
Causing trouble.
Oh, I like the little alternating thing I have going on here.
Let me connect like this.
Something like that.
Oh, yeah!
Okay, hold on.
Coffee?
Newspaper?
We're gonna have a stone path?
Speaking of stone, I need to go get some.
It's time to make some stone happen.
Also, it looks like there's honey.
We're gonna grab that now.
That would probably be near the enchanting.
Nine.
Ah, wait.
We need a campfire for that one.
Sticks.
I think I have that somewhere.
In fact, can I just leave it?
I'm gonna do an experiment.
Let's try and leave this beneath the bees.
Wait, do I even need to do this?
I think that's...
Fricking.
Health to the yeah!
Now I must have like three or so.
Or four even.
Where did I keep my honey?
We got two.
Okay, so we have three now.
Cool.
Let's keep those in the enchanting box.
Or the brewing box.
Is it morning?
Oh yeah.
Cheers, guys.
I feel like I've made insane progress here.
I'm no longer gonna hate looking at my house.
The house looks good.
This doesn't look good, though.
This does not look good.
I don't know what to do about this.
Maybe I...
I
don't know what to do here.
I guess I could add another window.
But now it's fine like that.
It's not amazing, but you know.
That's the charm of it!
It's not perfect.
It is a little rambunctious.
What else am I gonna do here?
I think it's time to go get some stones.
Or...
Actually, let's invest time into trying to get stone automatically.
So we have a drill, right?
And we can put it on a...
On a railroad?
You also got scaffolding.
Maybe we can make that look good somewhere.
Some scaffolding there.
Just random scaffolding.
You know, out and about.
It's okay.
Where's my stone?
Here.
Put all this in.
Let's just clean up the inventory a little bit here.
Glass also belongs in here.
Ah, ran out of space.
Hey, Jackie.
What do you want?
No, it's not food until 30 minutes from now.
Let me see.
And you still have food!
But maybe you just wanna play.
She's rubbing her head against my mouse!
I may actually have to close the door pretty soon when I start streaming.
Because it is getting kind of annoying.
And there's hairs everywhere.
I really don't like that.
Let me get these hairs off.
Purchase.
Put them in there.
Yeah, obviously the organization right now is not great.
But let's get ready for some railroad action.
Dude, we have an andeside ladder!
Let's put that here.
I can climb up like this if I want to.
You know, eeeh!
I also have another cauldron.
Let's have that next to the brewing.
That looks good.
Okay, so!
What we need...
is...
this.
And we need this.
And obviously we're gonna need some tracks.
Track, track, track, track, track, track.
There we go.
64 should do it.
Don't need more than that.
Maybe I bring some redstone stuff.
Maybe like a lever.
I need something to flip.
Let me see here.
Lever.
What the hell is that?
Wait a sec.
We just unlock something new.
Physics assembler.
Whoa.
Okay.
I'll keep it in mind.
Alright.
Not yet though.
So hold on.
This is the plan.
We're gonna put down some tracks.
Yeah.
Well.
I know what the plan is.
This is what we need.
We have tracks.
Redstone.
We can put that in here for now.
Saplings.
Let's just throw you in here.
And the cobblestone in there.
Yep.
Okay.
Don't need these sticks.
Not really.
I want to clean my inventory as much as possible before we start.
Can I cook some food?
While I'm gone.
Doesn't look like it.
I think we're about ready.
I'm gonna put on my goggles for this.
You can't go digging without goggles, right?
Where are thou?
Where are my goggles?
Bro, why can I not see them?
Ah!
There they are.
Yeah.
This needs to be fixed.
One thing at a time, though.
So I have this.
I have that.
Oh, I need some kind of block.
So I guess that would be...
I don't know.
Some kind of wood.
Like in the animation.
Obviously, it's gotta be dark oak.
Let's take...
One.
No, I don't like dark oak, actually.
Let's do...
An oak.
A simple oak plank.
No, one oak lock.
Just to clean up inventory.
That's it.
That's what we need.
And...
Then we need a wrench.
Of course.
Wrench.
Oh, God.
Where are you?
There you are.
Nice.
I think I'll bring a shield as well, just in case there's monsters.
It's looking good.
We don't need the golden boots right now.
Oh, Stuart!
I thought a creeper was inside my house.
Stuart, you bastard.
You scared me.
How's it hanging?
Oh, this is what I want!
I'm probably gonna unlock some stuff with that.
Nautilus shell.
I'm not even sure where you got it from.
Like, how do you get that?
I used to get a lot of it, but...
It's just slippery.
Weightless.
Okay.
Stuart, I am too poor for you.
Sorry.
I can't afford it.
I wish I could, but I can't.
Oh, we're also missing some...
Uh, you know what?
I will focus on that right now, just to get it done.
I gotta get that done right now, so I don't...
forget later.
And out here.
Oh, we're already done!
Great.
That was it.
Maybe this one.
There we go.
Pretty.
Yep.
Okay, I think we got everything we need.
Got the wrench.
We got, uh, torches for lighting.
Let's try it, shall we?
Let's find a place to dig.
I'm gonna go down into the mines.
Ah, I'm gonna bring a bed, just in case shit goes wrong.
Who knows?
Also...
Ah, I can't let that stand!
I gotta fix it.
There's one.
Oh, wait.
My items are in here now.
I'm so used to them being outside.
I forgot what I was doing just now.
What was I getting?
Shit!
Wait!
I was gonna dig.
I was gonna...
Oh, bed!
Bed!
Bed.
Bed is in here.
Yep.
There it is.
Now I'm ready.
Let's go.
Ah, I should have brought my bow.
Nah, it's fine.
The question is, where do I...
wanna do this?
I mean...
First off, we gotta try a...
proof of concept here.
Let's do it right here.
Right here.
This is it.
Watch.
So basically, this is my idea.
We're gonna make a little preliminary...
pre-tunnel?
A PT?
Let's just try that.
Ah!
I forgot the minecart!
God damn it!
It's like the one thing I needed.
Shit.
Minecart.
And what else do I need possibly?
Let me think.
So I start that.
I put the thing on the thing.
It's gonna go...
It's gonna go in.
It's gonna...
Turn it.
Rub it.
Smash it.
And I...
Oh, maybe a chest, actually.
Maybe there's a way to automatically collect the things as well.
That would be even better.
Maybe I need powered rails, too, now that I think about it.
Hmm.
Interesting.
Oh!
You know what?
We need more than one drill!
Drill!
Brother!
Andesite, iron, alloy.
Andesite, iron...
Wait.
Alloy.
Drill!
Let's make...
Five.
So that means we're gonna get...
Uh...
One, two, three, four, five.
Six of these?
You heard me right.
Put that back in here.
Stuart, you're not gonna believe what I'm about to do.
It's gonna blow your tiny little mind.
You've never seen some shit like this.
I have suddenly gained access...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Fucking mine cart!
Mine cart.
Where are you?
We just need one.
One mine cart?
Okay.
We put the thing on the mine cart.
Then we have the things on the...
We need glue!
Dude, I left home at first thinking I had everything.
Boy, was I wrong!
Now put this in again.
Anticide is heavy, apparently.
Interesting.
Okay, now I have everything!
We got it all.
Just gonna light my way here.
Just for the future.
Uh-oh.
Good.
I'm so excited for this.
This is gonna be wild.
Oh, then we do, uh...
Hold on.
There.
Here.
Oh, wait.
I guess we can do this.
Technically.
Hold on.
I'm getting some crazy ideas all of a sudden.
Wait.
Hold on.
We're not gonna use wood.
There's no way that's gonna...
Have, uh...
You know, survive the stress.
Of this ordeal.
Oh, I can't...
Oh.
That's fine.
We don't need this.
This hole is already made!
We only need a round it.
Of course.
Yeah!
Dup, dup, dup.
Now!
Here come the drills.
Oh, why are you doing that?
What the?
Why?
Is it trolling me?
Okay.
Oh, I thought I had more drills.
You know what?
That's fine.
We're gonna make a little pattern here.
Ah.
Dude, I like that.
That's nice.
And now?
Can I...
Wait.
Can I not somehow...
Uh...
Wait a minute.
Cancel.
Cancel!
Stop.
Okay.
Whatever.
I guess we're doing this.
Right?
Boom!
Connected!
Now watch.
Oh, oh!
We also gotta do this.
Oh, no.
I can't see it now.
I pushed it onto it!
Wait, what now?
Oh, my God.
No.
What is happening right now?
Which way is it facing?
I can't tell!
That way.
Okay.
Oh.
Lock rotation.
That's what we need.
Is it still connect, though?
It is connect, though.
Very good, yo.
All right.
You ready?
Ah, wait a minute.
We need power for this son of a gun.
Huh.
You know what?
I just had an idea, guys.
Check it out.
This is even better.
Who says we need to do it exactly here?
We can also do it to the right.
We're going to move everything over to the right.
Hopefully the minecart is not going to tip over.
You'll see what I mean.
Just like that.
That way I can see what's going on, and it's going to be glorious.
Yeah.
Is it connected?
It is not.
How do I unconnect?
Can I somehow see that?
Yeah?
Yeah.
Ah-ha!
Punch it with the glue item in hand.
Oh!
Smart!
And then here.
And here.
That should do it.
Now we need power.
Powered on?
Are you ready?
Here we go!
Go!
Wait a minute.
Yeah!
It's working!
Come on!
Push!
Put your pack into it!
Oh my god.
It's genius.
Dude, look at the digging efficiency!
That's amazing!
Obviously, we have some shortcomings here.
We're going to work out those kinks.
Hold up.
But this is a great start.
Wait, why is it not?
Oh, there we go.
There we go.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
You went off track.
Back on the track.
Do I have to push you back on it?
Wait!
The freaking...
Look!
It's because it's glued!
Dude!
Wait, why can't I?
Oh, does it need to go on the thingy first?
We can make the thingy.
There.
Come with me.
Turn it on.
No, off.
And then back.
Back, back, back, back, back.
Jackie?
No, no, no!
Come on!
Oh, no, uh...
It's not doing what I wanted to do.
So we go...
We go...
Wait.
I need to make room for myself.
We're gonna do this.
That's it!
Look at that!
It's wonderful.
Uh...
Oh.
Wait, uh, wait.
Where did my lever go?
Is it underneath the rock?
Oh!
I see it.
Let's put it on the other side.
Here?
No, no, no, no, no.
You go back.
Stay there.
Good.
In fact, I may have to...
Okay, that's good.
That's good.
Very good.
Uh, okay.
So basically...
Let me think.
How would I do this?
I guess I could use powered rails.
Powered rails or I go downhill.
Downhill is gonna be automatic because of gravity.
Um...
Or I find some way...
To automate...
Walls and grommets.
We put down the tracks as we go.
We would have to use a deployer for that.
Well, that sounds kind of crazy.
That sounds like it's gonna take...
Galaxy brain IQ...
Move...
Moves.
And I don't have those right now.
How would that even work?
I guess you would have some kind of repository of...
Tracks...
That you feed into the deployer.
And it's gonna...
Because every time the deployer does something...
It's an extension of me.
It's AI, right?
It's going to...
Right click as if it was a human.
Or...
Oh, wait a minute.
Why don't I just dig with that?
Can I put a...
Pickaxe...
In the deployer and just go...
I put a pickaxe with efficiency 5...
On the fucking deployer.
Who needs a digging machine?
Dude!
I mean, obviously I would need to do that first, but...
Um...
Oh, you know what would be really nice here instead of this?
Glass.
So we can see through.
Oh, I guess we can't see through this, but...
Let me, um...
Hmm.
Wait a second now.
Do we even need rails?
Rails.
This thing moves on its own!
Look!
Oh my god!
Dude.
I figured it out.
We're going off rails, baby!
Are you ready?
Here we go!
Dig for me!
Dig...
Uh-oh.
We're going in random directions.
Oh no.
Turn, turn...
Oh, oh no, no, no, no, no.
Oh no, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This way, this way.
Yes!
I mean, it's obviously a little slower.
If I can find something to push this...
It's, it's, it's digging.
I like that it's rotating around the minecart.
That's kind of cool, isn't it?
Also, what's, what's happening to all the materials coming out?
Oh, they're just sitting there.
Let me test something.
Oh, I forgot to bring the damn chest.
If I make a chest now...
I'll be back.
We gotta, uh...
Maybe I'll grab the deployer, too.
I need to do some experiments here.
Deployer with a...
Uh...
Tom Holland on, on top.
What's, what's it called?
A fucking...
Uh...
A, um...
The thing that goes down.
Forgot the name of it.
It's not a colander.
It is something...
Like it.
It is called...
Dude, I've, I've had...
Uh, wait.
Hop, hopper.
How the fuck did I go Holland?
Uh, chest.
Iron ingot.
So I'm gonna need another chest.
I need two chests, actually.
That's two of them.
Um, ingot...
Is in here.
Uh...
Hopper.
I need to do a quick experiment!
The hand.
Hand!
Uh...
I hope this is gonna spin or...
Work its magic without me spinning it.
Otherwise we'll have to grab some gears and do some kind of crazy contraption.
We'll have to see how that works.
Um...
I need to do a quick experiment here.
Show me a wheel.
Uh, yeah.
I mean, that's good enough for me.
For a quick test, at least.
No.
How do I make it not do that?
Oh!
It was poking me!
Look at that!
Let me see that achievement.
Place in power a deployer.
The perfect reflection of yourself.
Assemble a precision mechanism.
Can I make that?
Dude, this looks...
This is 100% like belt territory.
This is where you want the belt.
Transport items here.
Transport items there.
Here.
And comes out, you know.
Random salvage!
That's interesting.
Okay.
Uh, but how do I make it...
Just go down?
Uh, maybe I need to...
Wait.
Dirt.
Maybe I pointed at that.
No?
God damn it.
It's not intuitive at all how to...
Dude, stop!
Just point down!
It's going everywhere but down!
What is fucking going on here?
How do I do this?
Do I have to...
Do this, and then do this, and then...
Put it like that?
Stop!
This is horrible.
Why is it so hard?
Okay, there we go.
No, it's pointing up!
Oh my god!
This makes no sense.
Wow!
That's how you do it.
This is a little...
I don't know.
The way that looks...
Hmm.
I'm not gonna say it!
But, you know.
You know.
I'm not saying it.
It looks a little funky.
Let me grab something else here.
I need the little thing I saw.
Hold on.
Priss...
This thing.
What's that called?
Depot.
Casing, alloy.
Easy.
I have it.
Oh!
It's adjusting to the...
Oh, that's cool.
Okay.
So, wait a minute.
Let me try this, actually.
Alloy on...
Yeah, okay.
I'm gonna try that real quick.
I wanna see how this works.
Whoops.
Dude, I keep thinking there's an animal coming into my home.
So, we have the al...
Uh, casings.
And we have the alloys there.
So, all we need is wood.
Stripped wood.
Uh, where is it?
Ah, but wait a minute.
How do I give this thing the thing?
No, wait.
Oh, shit.
How do I get that out?
Oh, no.
Wait.
Oh, did I do it?
Oh, it's holding it!
Look!
I get it now.
I understand.
But I don't know how to get...
Oh, there we go.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Got it, got it, got it.
So, let me try something else.
This is the next stage.
Let's pretend that we have some floor here, right?
Oh, watch this.
Uh, actually, I have it, I have it.
First, we gotta endure this again.
Okay, I know how to do it now.
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
Maybe...
Yeah!
Okay!
Very nice.
But wait.
Let me try something else.
What if I do it this way?
Is it somehow gonna put it here?
Ah, shit, it's not rotating.
Um...
How do I solve that?
I guess I can point it the other way.
Yeah, that works.
So, let me do...
this.
Because, think about it.
If it is applying something to a block...
Well, I guess it's not pointing directly at the surface.
That's the problem.
So, yeah, maybe it's not gonna work, but...
It is gonna work!
Well, okay!
Never mind!
Oh, why did I just destroy?
The fan.
Okay, whatever.
Dude, this is insane.
Now the question is...
Is it gonna work automatically on the contraption?
And...
Something else we need to check real quick.
Let me put this back.
Let's say I were to put a hopper on top.
Oh, no.
It looks a little funky, but okay.
Bear with me.
Wait, why is it...
Where are these going?
It's holding one, but...
Oh!
Look, item rail X-30.
It's filling it.
There's like a little deposit inside of here, where it goes.
Oh, sick!
You don't even need the hopper, technically.
I mean, depending on how many this can hold.
Okay, get ready.
You're about to see some serious shit.
Let me think.
Dude, we need...
We need more...
More drill.
Yes.
Am I missing something?
Let me think.
We got...
Okay.
Whoa!
Maybe...
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Maybe there's a way to automatically destroy the rails behind you?
Bring them back to the front.
And keep laying them down.
Okay, let's take it one step at a time, though.
But that sounds crazy.
Because I was like, I only have 40-something.
You know?
Yo.
Actually.
There's still a problem, though.
Hold on.
We have a problem still.
It's not going to move on its own.
So we need powered rails.
That are constantly powered.
Wait.
How the fuck are we going to do that?
Wait a sec.
Let me see if this works first before we do anything.
I just want to, you know.
This thing scares me a little bit now.
Oh!
Oh my god.
That is fucking terrifying.
Get on the rails.
Get on the damn rails.
Move!
Why are you not moving?
Dude, get on the rail.
There we go.
We're on the rail.
Now we un-power?
Dude, it's like...
Wait.
It's automatically rotating?
Why is that happening?
Wait.
It's moving on its own?
Why is it moving on its own?
Oh!
You want to be free?
Is that it?
Hold on.
No, no, no, no, no.
Get back on it!
There we go.
Okay.
Let me try something else.
No, no, no.
First things first.
Dude, this is some...
This is some crazy stuff.
Let me disassemble the whole thing.
We need to build this from scratch.
Also, my torches are here.
Some lights.
That way.
Ah, I should have brought glass.
Nah, it's okay.
We'll deal without it.
So, here's the idea, right?
There.
So, I guess I want to...
Put this down here.
Oh, but I can't.
Yes, I can.
Because these are not going to be here.
Technically.
Not yet.
Yes.
Stop destroying that.
Like this.
But, but, but, but, wait.
How is this going to be powered?
Is...
Maybe it just is going to be...
Let me see.
Shit.
Oh, but, but, but, but, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We haven't, we haven't connected them.
Right.
Here we go.
Ah, there's an achievement for that.
Self-driving card.
I didn't even need, I didn't even need to look in here.
This was...
Where is it?
Self-driving.
Bro.
Oh, oh.
Create a mine card contraption that places tracks in...
Dude.
I saw that before even looking at this.
But I guess it's the natural thing to think about.
Okay.
Oh, wait, what?
Oh, it's because I have Silk Touch.
This is a new thing for me now.
Oops.
Get rid of this.
All right.
So, let me try with the thing on now.
Wait, it has 52 of them right now.
Wait, why can't I...
Stack them?
53.
Okay.
Oh my god, it's working.
So now we need drill.
But wait a minute.
We need to drill in front of this too.
Wait a second.
This is getting a little funky.
We need to drill...
Oh, no.
That's not gonna...
Let's do one more.
It's looking a little weird.
Okay, I understand.
But bear with me.
There's a reason behind the madness.
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait.
Okay, so this is gonna...
Yeah.
I feel like I need some...
Like a counterweight in the back here.
This is looking...
Just put something there, you know?
Just for my sanity.
Something like that.
Hahaha.
Man, this one minecart is gonna...
Woo!
Okay, and now...
The best way to do this, I guess, is to start removing everything.
And then...
There.
Here.
Move it all the way down.
And...
Oh, wait a sec.
Here.
This goes here.
Oh, shit.
There.
How about...
Wait, no.
What about these?
Wait, this is getting...
Hold on.
Start over.
I feel like I'm not doing this efficiently.
Let's start.
Okay, start here.
And move all the way back...
To there.
Ah?
That's more like it.
And then...
Oh!
Oh my god.
What the fuck just happened?
What the hell?
What is going on?
Huh?
Why are these...
Oh!
I see what's happening.
Oh, no.
Oh, crap.
I see the problem.
Oh, no.
I need to assemble it again.
Ah, shit.
All of this is part of the physics now.
Whoops.
Can I do this in an easy way, please?
Please get back on it.
Get back on it.
Please don't kill me.
What are you doing back there?
You're digging.
Okay.
Can you stop spinning?
Get back on the thing!
We're almost there.
Get on it.
Yeah, we're almost there.
Yeah!
Oh, my gosh!
Okay.
Dude, this...
Okay, dude.
Man, I don't like that it's down here now!
Uh-oh.
Did I just remove something I shouldn't have?
No, I didn't.
Okay, good.
Yes, I did.
Ah, damn.
Okay.
Remove the thingy!
Remove it all.
Off you go.
Is it gone?
Everything's gone.
Okay, so check it out.
This is what we're gonna do.
We start here.
Wait, before I even do that.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Let's just...
Stop, stop, stop!
No more, no more!
I don't want no more.
We're going to put...
The minecart below...
On the track...
Make a little bit of room here.
Uh, here.
This one.
Lever.
Get rid of this.
You know, we don't need this counterweight.
I changed my mind.
It's just gonna overcomplicate things.
Now.
Glue.
We start...
Here.
We bring it down.
And then...
Is that...
Are they connected now?
I think they're connected.
Turn it on.
Are you ready?
Wait, let me make sure this one is in the correct...
Lock it.
You ready?
Here we go.
Oh, wait.
Oh, they were not connected!
Oh, my goodness.
Ah!
Get back on the fucking rails.
There we go.
Okay.
Let's try that again.
I don't understand.
Why can't I remove it now?
Wait, are you connected now?
Why the fuck are you not connected?
There we go.
That has to be it.
Yeah.
I think.
Go back.
Slightly.
Here.
There.
Go!
It's digging!
Ah!
Wait, we have a problem.
Shit.
They need to be moved down.
Come on.
Oh!
Oh, yoy, yoy, yoy, yoy, yoy, yoy, yoy.
Back on the track.
Come on.
Push it.
Back on the track.
This is a little janky.
I'm not gonna lie.
Dude, what's happening?
Get on the...
Okay, here we go.
Shit.
Oh.
Turn off!
Oh, thank god.
Okay, we gotta move everything down one.
We're almost there.
No?
Oh.
Oh, that's a cool way of doing it.
Okay.
Okay, now.
It's all connected, right?
Let me...
We don't need this top part.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, whoa.
Yeah.
Maybe?
Oh, dude.
I don't trust it.
We're gonna start over.
Start over with the glue.
We start here.
Yeah.
And then?
That is connected, baby.
You ready?
Go!
Wait, no, no.
Why are you not doing...
Oh, wait.
Oh, shit!
Back!
Go back again.
Okay.
We're almost there.
You know what?
I just had an idea.
No, never mind.
Bad idea.
You know what?
Maybe I don't need this.
I put the thing directly.
Huh?
I like that.
I like it.
Filled.
Good.
And now?
Rails.
I need a couple rails, please.
Mode?
Oh, mode.
Oh!
Mode attack and use!
Look at that!
Interesting.
Give me these.
I need a couple myself.
In.
Wait, you're not gonna...
Hold on.
We have a problem here now.
We need to go one further.
Like that.
And then?
Oh, no.
Wait, does...
Wait a sec.
I can also...
Oh, I have a better idea, actually.
Why do I do it like that when I can just go down?
Right?
Wait, this is a much better idea.
Dude, we could even...
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, hold up.
I see what's going on here.
Just freaking do it like this.
Look at that!
Much easier.
Then we remove this, even.
And...
Oh, dude!
We could even...
Oh...
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
We're gonna make this a compact boy.
It's gonna be way better.
Okay, so...
This is gonna...
Right there.
Okay?
Just gonna put it right there.
And...
Wait, maybe it needs to be one further ahead.
Actually, no, it doesn't.
No, no.
It does not.
It needs to be right there.
And then we put...
Uh, this thing...
Here.
Actually, we don't even need that!
We can just do, like, this.
Here.
No!
Wait, how am I gonna do this, then?
Maybe I'm not.
Ah!
There we go.
No good.
No bueno.
So I do this, and then I remove it.
Wait, I wonder if these can stay together with glue and not...
Do we even need these rocks?
Wait a minute!
I can glue it!
We're totally just gluing this shit!
Now watch.
Get rid of everything.
Here.
There.
There!
I need to double-check everything before we go.
Plops.
Dicks.
I think we got it.
Oops.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no.
That's not...
Part of it.
Okay, here we go.
You ready?
Oh, wow, wow.
Oh.
There we go.
There we go!
Look at that!
Yo!
Dude, that is sick!
Would you look at this?
Oh, we're gonna be tunneling so much...
Oh.
I...
I am the bitch.
I will collect these and keep feeding.
Yes, I will.
I'm ready.
Oh, ho, ho!
Wow!
Let me see.
Wait, it's losing...
It's losing speed.
Oh, okay, hold on.
We have a problem, then.
I thought it would go on forever.
Right, I guess I could push it, but...
Oh, the funny thing is...
It actually...
It retains its momentum, even after digging.
Yo, this is amazing.
Come on.
Oh, it's even faster now.
Wow.
Here, I got more for you.
Take it.
Dude!
The possibilities are crazy here.
Wait, am I...
Look at all the cobblestone I'm collecting!
Whoa!
Hold up.
This is kind of nuts.
Wait, is all the cobblestone...
Concentrated up front?
Oh, it is.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my God!
Yo.
Oh, my goodness.
Wow.
Faster.
Come on, come on.
What?
Dude!
Oh.
Yeah, I was about to say.
What happens then?
Oh.
Hopefully, it's not going to fall down.
We're going to have to make a little test here.
It does fall down.
Now, what is the easiest way to stop this thing from...
physicking?
No more physicking.
Wait.
I think I need this thing.
I actually have an idea for how to solve that issue just now.
We need two deployers.
We need a deployer below the deployer to put rocks so that it's never going to fall.
But the thing is, what if it's like a four block gap?
Then we can't do it.
Or, let's say...
I guess it's the range it has, right?
Let's say I have range there right now.
This is like the range I have.
So, if the drop is more than that...
Also, it's not going to do it fast enough.
It's going to go...
Blop.
You know, so...
Place your card assembly...
Yeah.
Okay.
It's got to be an easier way to fucking get this thing non-physicalized.
Wait, where am I?
It's not that bad, I guess.
Uh, well, that was very illuminating.
I'll be taking all of this with me.
I have plans for this for sure.
I don't need this.
I wonder if I can give it silk touch.
Like, putting the pickaxe in front like I talked about.
I just got so much material.
I'm happy.
I'll come back for that chest later, I guess.
I just want to do one last test back here at the house.
I need to see something.
Oh, I love that I can see my little house in the distance.
Look at the windows.
How does it look when I come from here?
Let me see.
What is it missing?
Oof.
Guys, it's very brown.
This needs stone.
So check it out.
Proof of concept.
I'm thinking...
Just the front and the backs.
To break it up.
You'll see what I mean.
And obviously, we're going to change this to also contain some...
Maybe some mossy cobblestone and some stone.
And whatever the other ones are called.
The ones with the bricks.
Give me that.
Okay, whatever.
Dude, hell yeah.
This is going to look amazing.
I'm going to get this broken up a little, you know?
With some different types of blocks.
To not make it look so uniform.
But that is the general idea.
Imagine all of this as well.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Definitely.
Can I blast that?
Man, why can I not blast that, you know?
That's crazy.
So, uh...
Stones, we would have to turn into...
Let me see.
Stone...
Oh, that's...
Right.
Bricks.
And minifix.
It's an evil company.
Apparently.
So we would put some of this in there.
You know, maybe one like here.
Maybe something like that.
You see the vision?
I know you see it.
And then out here...
We're going to make a path.
Yes!
We're even going to make more.
Let me actually make a preliminary outline for the path.
And I'm envisioning the path to go towards the little lake.
You know?
Nice little lake.
We're going to pass by this little tree here.
We're going to make a right turn.
Dude, I'm still, like, half high from that digging session just now.
Oh, that was freaking incredible.
We can get infinite stone.
We can make tunnels.
We can make bridges.
Nothing will stop us now.
Nature is under my thumb.
And not only that.
We will not stop at stone.
We will be sawing things.
We will be clawing at things.
We will be longing for drinks.
And watch how it connects!
This is it!
The path goes here!
We have a little thing going down.
You see it?
We're going to put mossy cobblestones on the edges near the grass.
And he saw that it was beautiful.
Incredible.
And now we have all this dirt as well we can use outside!
I'm going to put it here!
We're going to bury our house in dirt.
Inventory efficiency has been activated.
Everything shall get buried in dirt.
Not just the women or the children.
But the cats.
And the dogs too!
Everyone gets buried by sand.
And tiny pebbles.
It's glorious.
Look at it go.
And the bees are here.
What a vibe.
I have tears in my eyes.
It's so pretty.
What's up, friend?
Your butt is still dirty as hell.
Just so you know.
It's full of...
Whatever that is.
Bee stuff.
Can I actually grab with my bucket?
I can't.
Let's grab a glass bottle.
Just while we're at it here.
Back here.
I need just one, actually.
You know what?
I've had it with you up there.
We got it.
More honey for my honey business.
I had it back here, I think.
Four honeys.
Can I do something with that?
I can make a honey block?
Let's do it.
Okay.
I can turn it back to potions.
But...
Wait, that's it?
I for sure thought I was gonna unlock something.
Put this back in here.
And this is cooking.
Wonderful.
Stone.
How do I make it mossy?
I guess I'd have to get some moss.
How do I get moss?
Or even this moss?
Let me grab this dirt here before it disappears.
Dude, tell me this isn't looking amazing.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, definitely we need moss.
Moss, moss, moss.
Oh!
There's a little cave down here, too.
It's kind of fun.
Man, that's a day's hard work.
Great way to stop it there.
Great.
Whoops.
Turn it back.
What do you think of that?
Wasn't that successful?
How did you like the digging?
I sure love the digging.
Ah.
Man.
This is...
Like, I don't think I have fully grasped the potential that we have in front of us here.
That digging machine is going to do so much work for me.
I will be making tunnels everywhere.
In fact, I will be bringing that into the nether as well.
I have so many ideas already with the digging machine.
It's going to be wild.
Yeah, belts are still a cliffhanger.
I don't want to, you know, cash in on that enjoyment yet for myself.
I have that to look forward to.
I'm just getting all the basic stuff done out of the way, you know?
I want my house nice because I know if I start to work with belts, and I can tell you this a hundred percent, if I start to work with belts and I try to connect little grabby arms and I try to make like a whole sequence of things that are happening, I will never be able to stop and I will never finish my house.
The house will never be done.
So I got to take care of that first.
At least most of it.
And then we can, you know, make it better down the road.
For example, I need the belts to get the andeside casings.
So I can make the floor even better.
Because right now we're at 82%.
And we got to get to 110.
Good things take time.
And look at how much progress I made today in like four hours.
I feel like my whole situation is unrecognizable compared to last time.
The thing is though, the backyard factory is going to look nice, okay?
It's going to be a green factory.
But we're still going to, you know, pollute us all hell.
It's just going to look green on the outside.
Just like real life.
We're going to have green stickers and, you know, all that.
But really, we're going to pollute.
Not going to lie, you inventing the driller by yourself was beyond impressive.
Was it though?
I don't think it was.
I think it was quite logical.
You got the drill, right?
Obviously, you want to try and drill rock.
And then you're like, okay.
Let's put it on the mine cart.
Because we want to go drill in the mines, right?
So you need the rails.
But then you're automatically like, oh, I don't want to be pushing this every time.
So how do we put down rails?
It's all really amazingly developed.
This mod is incredible.
The progression is real.
It makes so much sense.
Why do you refuse to use create tools?
What do you mean?
Did you not see my digging machine?
I literally made a digging machine that dug through the mountain.
Please don't put a tower in the house.
Sewer Steward, now I will put a tower in the house.
Next stream is going to be a tower stream.
In fact, it's going to be a rectangular tower.
And on top, we're going to have trees.
And you know what it's going to be made of?
Copper.
Green copper.
And the normal copper.
Yo, a cockwheel tower sounds amazing.
Made of cock?
I love it.
You always talk to Jackie in English?
No, I don't.
Actually, sometimes I do.
Depending on what I say to her.
But mostly I speak Danish.
Sometimes I speak German to her as well.
She's getting a little bit of everything.
She speaks cats, Mr. Tanuki.
I don't know.
She doesn't really have a language.
Polyglot, yeah.
How do you say Jackie in Danish?
Exactly the same way.
I say Jackie.
Jackie.
It's the same.
There's no difference.
Cranking tower?
Maybe I will crank my tower.
If it ends up being ugly.
Because that is one way to destroy it immediately, right?
Oh, wait a minute.
You were making a sexual euphemism with that.
I didn't even realize.
I thought you meant that I was going to make an ugly tower, and then I was going to manually crank it to destroy it, just like I do trees.
That's what I thought you meant, but then when everyone did the huh, you know, then I was like, oh, I get it now.
Wow.
I'm a little slow on that.
Cog tower that becomes a rocket.
Dude, I'm going to the moon.
So, I think you're right.
Sounds like a specific company, actually.
A company logo.
The thing you're describing there.
Could you educate me as to what will happen inside the clock tower?
Well, we're going to have clocks and gears, and we're going to have a big clock, actually.
It's going to be a clock tower.
And I'm going to have a bell up there, and you know what?
We're going to have a deployer on the bell going bing!
It just occurred to me we can do that.
We can right-click a bell.
Dude!
We're going to be binging!
And dinging!
And donging!
That is amazing.
Wow, I just had that realization we can do that.
Dude, the deployer is actually kind of mind-blowing.
Because it can literally do everything you can do.
By the way, did anyone ever figure out what happened to the ding guy?
Like, why did that happen?
If you even remember him.
Automatic gym button, you're right!
Kado Kako!
You're a genius!
We're going to have a button that does nothing up top.
And we're going to have 20 different brewing stands for a timer.
In sequence.
And then we're going to have the hand go on the button.
So it says, Jim.
It's beautiful.
Did you delete your old world?
I actually don't know where it is.
I can't find it.
I may have deleted it.
But I'm pretty sure I made a backup somewhere, guys.
It may be somewhere on a hard drive or something.
Oh, no, no.
I thought you meant my old world from Season 2.
No, no.
Obviously, the world from...
From this season.
The first one.
Is deleted, yes.
That one is gone, I'm pretty sure.
I did not make a backup of that one.
Maybe I can try and dig up the world for Season 2.
Because some people were asking for it.
And honestly, yeah.
I don't mind giving that out.
I just don't think I have it.
But maybe I do.
I'm not sure.
Yeah, to find a Dinka.
Exactly.
Maybe you can investigate the world to get on that, you know.
I'll see if I can find it.
Maybe I have it on some hard drive somewhere.
Because I'm pretty sure I took plenty of backups back then.
Maybe not the most recent.
Version.
But there's definitely something somewhere.
Do Dinka guys attack axolotls?
I don't know.
Could be.
I don't know what was going on.
But he would sometimes appear and be dinging all over the place.
And it would be like a regular occurrence too.
Doesn't matter what time of day or whatever.
Would you ever consider adding more mods?
Probably not.
Not in this season.
But I was thinking about an idea for a future season.
In the very, very far future.
Where I simply let all of you design a crazy ass mod pack.
And then I go in fully blind.
Not knowing what to expect.
I think that could be really fun.
You know?
You guys design something bonkers.
Not too insane of course.
But something absolutely ridiculous.
Just filled to the brim with the craziest shit.
And I'm going in fully blind.
Not knowing what to expect.
I think that could be really fun.
And then on the day I do the stream.
You hand me the mod pack.
I install it.
And we go.
What do you think?
Couldn't that be fun?
I think it could be really fun.
Obviously it would have to be something that I could figure out on my own.
So not something over the top ridiculous, you know?
Ridiculous within reason.
If you know what I mean.
What do you know about RLcraft?
I don't know anything about that.
I don't know about any mods.
The only mod I've been playing regularly off stream is the genu...
I mean the um...
I forgot the name of it.
But there's a mod I played off stream.
I'm kidding.
Come on.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Oh my god.
I can't not laugh at that.
That is just too funny.
The comments on YouTube when I made that announcement with the little Jenny picture...
Was hilarious.
There were so many people who were convinced I was gonna do it.
And they were worried I was gonna get banned.
Like, no you can't do that.
You're gonna get banned, Oliver.
Don't do it.
You know?
I was having a blast reading those comments.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Little Jenny picture.
Yeah, exactly.
Do you have a plan to use the soundtrack from Beampode for streams?
Yeah, maybe.
Maybe at some point.
When I get tired of some other stuff or when I feel like it.
There was a moment where everyone on chat was speaking their native language.
It was fun.
Oh, really?
How many different nationalities do we have in here?
Is it more than 20?
It's gotta be, right?
Statistically, 800 people right now.
Which is insane, by the way.
800 people just sitting here.
In this stream.
No, it's not 500.
It's...
I would say probably 30.
Maybe...
Yeah, 30 or so.
If I were to guess.
So, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7...
8...
9...
Okay, I see a repeating 10.
Definitely 10.
Wow.
Yeah, there's people everywhere.
From all over the place.
Iceland.
Cool.
We're from El Salvador.
Russia.
Costa Rica.
Norway.
Wait, why is nobody saying United States?
Is nobody here from U.S.?
Statistically, there should be a lot of you.
Okay, if you're from the U.S., say you're...
States.
Let's see the states from the U.S.
Okay, Iowa.
Tennessee, Minnesota, Louisiana.
California.
Colorado.
Texas.
I've always wanted to go to Texas, actually.
Or what's that state where Bernie Sanders is from?
Vermont.
For some reason, I just imagined Vermont to be beautiful.
Am I wrong?
I feel like it has...
It would have nice nature.
It sounds like a place that has nice nature.
You're not wrong?
Vermont is beautiful.
You have, like, a bunch of nice trees and lakes and stuff, right?
You would like Idaho for the potatoes?
Yeah, dude, when I was visiting the U.S., I was not in Idaho.
I was in Baltimore.
But when I went to the supermarket there, you guys have, like, ten different types of potatoes you sell.
And they are named.
Like, russet potato and some others.
And you could choose that.
That's not something we have in Denmark at all.
Here we have, like, potatoes and new potatoes.
And maybe also sweet potatoes.
Yeah, sweet potatoes, too.
So that's all I know.
I love that I could just choose different types of potatoes.
When I watch recipes on YouTube how to make something, and they go, Oh, you want to use this type of potato for this dish?
I'm like, dude.
For me, a potato is a potato.
We don't really distinguish here.
Red potatoes and white potatoes.
Okay.
You're a potato farmer, Vision?
That's kind of cool.
I guess you have a lot of potatoes at home, like, for dinner?
Or do you get tired of it?
What is it, baked?
Maybe?
I mean...
I actually haven't put a potato in the microwave for...
Maybe a year, actually.
Isn't that kind of nuts?
I think I had too much of it at some point, and I just had to take a break.
Mr. Tanuki isn't actually proud of the corn in Iowa.
95% of it isn't fit for human consumption.
It's grown solely because the U.S.
government subsidizes it.
I see.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Ew, microwaving a potato?
Dude, you haven't been living, though.
Okay?
Don't even get me started on that.
Yes, if you have infinite time and infinite patience, the oven is better, technically.
But you can make a baked potato in the microwave be 95% as good as an oven potato.
I'm not even kidding.
If you do it right, it's six minutes only.
And it's incredible.
It's moist, it's juicy, it's crispy somehow.
I don't know how, but it is.
It's incredible.
You boil them, mash them, stick them in a stew.
You need to lift it on stilts.
I have never tried that in the microwave, actually.
I should try that.
That's a good idea.
Potatoes in general are S tier.
Yes, and you know what?
They are also the type of food that makes you the most full of all the food.
So if you're trying to lose weight, for example, right, and you have this problem of eating too much food, which is also something I suffer from, potatoes is the most filling food you can eat.
Like, it's not even close compared to other types of food.
So if you just eat a lot of potatoes in your diet, you're naturally not going to feel as hungry.
And it's super healthy too, at the same time.
Never put an egg in a microwave.
I've actually never tried, but I guess it would explode.
You just put the potato in there naked.
No, no, no.
So you would wash it first, right?
Ideally, you have the skin on, unless it's too dirty.
But you would wash the skin, you know, make it nice.
And then you would dry it off.
You would put some olive oil on top of it.
You would stick it with a fork, you know, so it doesn't explode in the microwave.
And then you rub it with some rough salt, okay?
Put it on a plate in the microwave, six to seven minutes, depending on the size of it.
When it comes out, you slice it down the middle.
Open it up, put some garlic butter in there or something, and...
Bop's your uncle.
So good.
Yes, Oliver's oil.
My oil, the one I produce.
You can find it on my merch store.
Go to olivermerch.com.
That's not a thing.
Maybe one day.
Maybe one day I'll start selling out completely.
And I will sell pillows and mugs.
In fact, I'll sell a mug with my mug on it.
What do you think about that?
I would buy...
What if I sold a mug with a potato on it?
Just a potato.
I feel like that's not...
It's too boring.
I don't know what to put on there.
Yeah, style is dead.
That would be a good one, actually.
Style is dead.
With a little circle.
Or the demon mug.
Okay, guys, I need to go.
Jackie is actually overdue for feeding.
Which is weird.
I guess she still has food left, but...
Yeah, I'm gonna go feed myself and Jackie.
And thank you so much for watching.
This day was amazing.
The house is almost done.
Next time, we're most surely gonna make an elevator.
And we're gonna make all kinds of cool stuff happen.
Thank you for watching.
I'll see you around.
Have a good Sunday.
Bye-bye.